Why do they say "AA"?
(Leonard:)Army Ants.
(Leonard:)Isn't that confusing? AA might mean
something else to certain people.
(Sheldon:)Why would a Physics Bowl team
be called Anodized Aluminum?
(Leonard:)No, I meant...
(Leonard:)Never mind.
(Leonard:)Hey, check it out.
(Leonard:)I got you a Batman cookie jar.
(Sheldon:)Oh, neat. What's the occasion?
(Leonard:)Well, you're a friend
and you like Batman and cookies...
(Leonard:)...and you're off the team.
SHELDON:
What?
(Leonard:)Howard, Raj and I
just had a team meeting.
(Sheldon:)- You didn't.
- We did. I just came from there.
(Sheldon:)I don't know where you just came from.
It couldn't have been a team meeting.
(Sheldon:)I'm on the team and I wasn't there.
Ergo, the team did not meet.
(Leonard:)Okay, let me try it this way.
(Leonard:)I was at a coffee klatch
with a couple of friends...
(Leonard:)...and one thing led to another
and, it turns out, you're off the team.
(Howard:)- Why?
- Because you're taking all the fun out of it.